[](javascript:void(0))

Software  

Company  

Privacy Policy
==============

**Owner and Data Controller**
Fatih Ramazan Çıkan
1751 Sk. No:14/1 32100 Merkez/Isparta Turkey
[\[email protected\]](https://vovsoft.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Vovsoft.com ("Vovsoft") is committed to protecting your personal information and respecting your privacy.

We will never sell, rent or disclose your personally identifiable information to outside parties without your consent.

We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that we have in our database the personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately at [https://vovsoft.com/contact/](https://vovsoft.com/contact/) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

With your permission, we may send you newsletter emails regarding new products, updates or other information. You may always opt-out of receiving newsletter emails through [https://vovsoft.com/newsletter/](https://vovsoft.com/newsletter/) or by clicking on the link provided at the bottom of our email to you.

We collect and process information that is reasonably necessary for our services. The types of information we collect and process depend on the specific service we provide to you. For instance, when you visit Vovsoft web site and/or submit a form, we collect and process your information. Additionally, our software products may establish connections to our web servers for license validation and update checks. In all these instances, we may collect and process data such as Cookies, Referrers, IP Addresses, and System Information.

A "cookie" is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. It can be used to provide you with a tailored user experience. Some Vovsoft pages use cookies. Cookies are used to better personalize the content and promotions that you and other users will see. We may use the information to research and understand how our users' habits in the aggregate are similar or different so that we can enhance your experience on Vovsoft web site and with our products. With your consent, cookies can optionally store information from forms that you fill out on our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. We do not require that you accept cookies.

A "referrer" is the information passed along by a web browser that references the web URL you linked from, and is automatically collected by our web servers. This information is collected and used by us to understand the web site referring traffic to our web pages and to present appropriate content to our potential customers. Referrer information is tabulated by us on an aggregated basis to identify general trends and traffic patterns.

"IP addresses" are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer so that data (such as the web pages you request) can be sent to you. They are automatically gathered by our web servers and used for abuse prevention purposes.

"System information" we gather includes language, time, type of software/browser being used, operating system/platform. This information is sent automatically by your device when you are connected to the Internet and is used by us for statistics. This information is used in identifying trends and may be used to provide information appropriate for your computer system.

At the time of product download and/or purchase, information you provide to us, including personal information and referring URL's, is collected and processed. Additionally, we may contact you via email concerning your product download and/or purchase, providing details such as the download link, license key information, and an invitation to review the product.

We disclose the information we collect when required by law or to respond to legal process. When permitted or required by law, we may share information with third parties for purposes including response to legal process.

Vovsoft web site contains links to other web sites. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

We respect your right to control your personal information. If you wish to delete your data from our records, please submit a deletion request at [https://vovsoft.com/contact/](https://vovsoft.com/contact/). Upon receiving such a request, we will review it in accordance with applicable laws and promptly take reasonable steps to delete the requested information from our database, unless retention is necessary for legal purposes. Please note that certain data may remain in our backups or archives for a limited period even after deletion, but it will not be actively used.

We revise our Privacy Policy to keep it up to date with Vovsoft products, services and web pages. We will notify you of any changes we make by posting an updated version of this policy on our web site. Any changes will take effect when they are so posted. We also post FAQ's from time to time on specific products.

We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy statement and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy statement. Because of the complex and constantly changing nature of technology and business, we do not guarantee error-free performance under this privacy statement. We shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this privacy statement.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our software or web site, or wish to make a complaint about our handling practices, you may contact us at [https://vovsoft.com/contact/](https://vovsoft.com/contact/). We will investigate any complaints received in writing and do our best to resolve them with you as soon as possible.

**Last Updated: January 6, 2024**

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
|  **Vovsoft Newsletter** |     |
| Updates Giveaways Special Offers |     |
|     |     |
|     |     |
| Join **60,000+** other subscribers.  <br><br>And don't worry, we hate spam too! You can [unsubscribe](https://vovsoft.com/newsletter/?p=unsubscribe) at anytime. |     |

**Contact Information**  

     VOVSOFT.COM © 2015 - 2024
